Welcome to this introductory practice.
Please find yourself a suitable and comfortable location.
It is better if the light is not too bright at this moment.
See if your location is safe and secure from any disturbance.
Keep your back straight.
Realize yourself with your surroundings.
Identify your precise location exactly where you are.
Be gentle with yourself and kindly accept whatever feelings emerge during this practice.
Channel love in your own direction using your mind, your heart and the energy of your total being.
Be kind to this body that you are about to observe.
Allow your eyes to relax and rest your gaze downward at a 45 degree angle approximately.
So that your eyes are relaxed.
Find a spot where your eyes can stabilize their gaze.
The purpose of this practice is to stabilize yourself presence and your mind while keeping the eyes open.
And resting peacefully in this safe and comfortable location.
Without concentrating on the single spot.
Allow your eyes to peacefully and passively gaze downward.
Without applying any strong focus, simply passively observe downward and start sensing your breathing.
Your attention gently moves towards the breathing observation.
Allow your eyes to passively gaze downward.
While you are beginning to observe your breathing body.
Observe your breathing process.
When thoughts arise, shift your mind towards the breathing process.
Allow your eyes to continue resting peacefully and observing downward without any concentration.
A passive gaze.
While you are observing your breathing body.
Observe how your body is breathing.
You are peacefully observing your breathing.
If you wish to close your eyes, you may do so and you may also keep them open.
Observe your breathing body.
In you to observe the breathing body.
Notice how the body is breathing.
Notice any sensations arising in your body.
Without reacting, continue the observation of your breathing body.
With eyes opened in a relaxed fashion.
With eyes closed, you continue to simply observe the breathing body.
You may hear the sounds around you if any.
While you are peacefully resting in your location.
Your eyes are not engaging with anything.
You may notice how the body is breathing by itself.
You are just a spectator of this peaceful process.
Observer of how the body is breathing by itself.
How everything is happening by itself.
And you are just simply present.
Without doing anything.
Presence.
Witness the natural breathing of the body.
Relax and witness this moment.
You are relaxed and peaceful.
Observer of your breathing body.
Of this moment.
This body.
This moment.
Thank you.