The purpose of this practice is…
The purpose of this practice is to turn the attention of the mind towards your breathing
body.
In this practice we navigate the mind from thoughts to the breathing process, to observing
the breath and sensations within the body.
We set ourselves to take the time to keep driving the mind from thinking to breathing.
Let us begin the process of self and breathing observation.
Identify your precise location.
Let us start by turning the mind inward towards your breath.
Notice the flow of the breath.
Turn your mind towards the breathing process.
Notice the air coming out of your body into your body.
Start observing the breathing process.
Notice the exhale.
Inhale.
From thinking to breathing.
From thought to breath.
Turn your mind towards observing your breathing.
Mind towards breathing.
From self-healing process.
Allow your body to breathe freely and naturally as it requires.
Watch the natural breathing process of your body.
Notice the flow of the breath.
From thought to breath.
From emotion to breath.
Back to the breathing body.
Observe the free and natural breathing of your body.
Let us patiently observe the breathing.
We have nothing else to do than to observe the breathing body.
We have nothing else to do.
Observe the sensations inside your body.
Continue observing.
Back to the breath.
From thought to breath.
From emotion to breath.
Observe your natural breathing.
Just wait here and keep observing the breath.
And observe.
Keep self-observe.
Keep your back straight.
Observe the breath.
Nothing to do.
Witness how the body is breathing by itself.
Witness the natural breathing process.
Witness your breath.
Your breath.
Witness breath.
Your presence.
Your breath.