Hello and welcome to the Self-Gravity Practice of our meditation program.
That is strongly related to the sense of self and developing the internal
presence. For this center of gravity plays as a crucial gateway to building this
internal self-presence.
Identify your precise location exactly where you are.
Let us trigger the practice by exhalation in a vertical, top-down fashion.
Exhaled from your nose, from your chest, finish with exhaling from the belly and emptying
your body of air. Exhaled from the nose, from the chest, pull the belly in to push out
air, pull it in a little more, imp to yourself completely of air, then allow your body
to breathing naturally. Shallow or deep as it wishes. Again, attention on the exhale from
the nose, from chest, from the belly, pull the lower belly in, push out the air, let your
body become empty of air. It can then easily inhale the air into your empty body.
Exhaling downward from the top, from your chest, from the belly. No need to focus on inhaling
but the body breathing by itself. Again, from the nose, from chest, from the belly.
Again, a vertical exhale, pull the belly in, push out the air.
Focus only on exhale, top-down, the vertical exhale.
Next, exhale, bring your attention towards your chest area. Exhale all the way down.
Next, exhale, bring your mind lower to the abdominal area.
Exhale from the belly, bring your mind lower to the waist, lower to the belly.
Exhale again, from the top, from the chest, from the belly and reach the point in your lower belly.
In the center, deep in the belly.
Use the exhalation to help you reach the point of gravity.
Reach the center of gravity.
Pull the belly in, push out the air and anchor in the center of gravity.
Use your exhale to help you anchor in the point of gravity.
Reach the center of gravity.
It arises, shift your mind from thinking to center.
Back to center.
Now, observe your center of gravity.
Let go of any breathing focus.
Go to the center, connect with the center of gravity.
Observe the center of gravity.
From thought to center.
To the center.
Back to center.
You may now raise your attention from the center upward towards the abdominal area.
Gently and slowly lifting up towards the chest.
Rising up to the center of the head.
Come out through the ears and hear every sound.
The sound of anything you can hear.
And slowly come back to the center of the head.
Lower to the throat, to the chest.
Down towards the center of gravity.
The mind, connecting to the center of gravity.
Establishing the vertical link from the center of gravity.
To the center of head.
The central link.
The vertical inner presence.
From the belly to the head.
From point of gravity to the chest to throat to the center of head.
Stay in this inner presence.
The inner vertical presence.
The home within.
From lower center to the middle to the upper center.
The vertical connection.
Knot to the center.
Let me climb up Mount Susvery and back.
Hit once more.
Move back to Mount Susvery home.
Turn right and use your hands.
Lead to Mount Susvery home.
Move back to Mount Susvery home.
Fold and tap over your lips.
Back to Mount Susvery home.
So, this is...
Front knee, back to Mount Susvery, back to Mount Susvery home.
Turn right and use my hands.
Turn back to Mount Susvery home.
.
Cover your eyes with your palms.
Cover your ears and hear yourself.
Cover your ears with your palms.
Bring the palms in front of your eyes.
Open your eyes.
On your palms.
The first thing you see is yourself.
Thank you.
.