Welcome to the three-minute guided meditation training by all here.
We will now begin five rounds consisting of three minutes each with one minute pause in between.
We shall begin the first round in ten seconds.
Round one. Visualize the cosmic sky.
Look at the night sky. See the stars.
See the cosmic sky.
Allow the stars to move closer to you and look at the dark space between the stars.
Look at the darkness.
Allow the stars to shift away as you move towards darkness.
See the dark space.
Look at the darkness, approaching your face.
Look at the dark.
End of round one.
Round two.
Visualize the full moon inside your chest.
Look at the full moon inside you.
The moon and the moonlight lighting up your chest.
Lighting up your stomach, your lungs, your shoulders.
Coming upward through your throat.
Look at the shining moon inside you.
See the full moon.
Full moon inside your chest.
The moon and the moonlight.
Beaming through your chest, lighting up your throat, your head.
See the full moon.
End of round two.
Round three.
Round visualize a star in your belly right in the center of gravity.
Look at the shining star, deep in your belly.
Rounded by darkness of the belly.
Sense the star and the starlight emanating from your center.
Lighting up through your body, the starlight shining vertically up to the center of your head.
Look at the shining star.
Keep looking.
The star, the starlight.
End of round three.
Round four.
Look at the star deep in the center of gravity.
Surrounded by darkness of the belly.
The starlight as the star fades away.
Look at the darkness surrounding the center of gravity.
At the darkness of the belly.
Deep in the belly.
Continue to look at the dark in the belly.
End of round four.
Round five.
Now visualize the cosmic sky in front of you.
Move closer to the stars.
You move beyond the stars towards the darkness.
See the deep dark beyond all planets, galaxies.
The darkness approaching to your face.
Touch the darkness.
Stay in the dark.
End of round five.
Round six.
Visualize a single star in the dark sky.
Any direction.
See how the star is moving closer to you.
Inside and forming into an image of sun in front of you.
And the sun light shining onto your face, onto your body, shining through.
The sun is moving closer.
The giant sun in front of you.
The light peers through your body as you enter the space of sun.
Enter the sun light lighting on the entire space.
You absorb into the sun.
You become the sunlight.
End of round six.