Welcome to the three-minute guided meditation training by all here.
We will now begin five rounds consisting of three minutes each, one minute pause in between.
We shall begin the first round in ten seconds.
Round one. Visualize the cosmic sky.
Look at the night sky.
See the stars.
See the cosmic sky.
Allow the stars to move closer to you and look at the dark space between the stars.
Allow the stars to shift away as you move towards darkness.
Look at the darkness.
See the dark space.
Look at the darkness, approaching your face.
Look at the dark.
Round two.
Visualize the full moon inside your chest.
Look at the full moon inside you.
The moon and the moonlight lighting up your chest.
Here's the dark.
Coming upward through your throat.
Look at the shining moon inside you.
See the full moon.
Full moon inside your chest.
Through your chest, lighting on your throat.
Your head.
See the full moon.
End of round two.
Round three.
Now visualize the star in your belly right in the center of gravity.
Look at the shining star.
Surrounded by darkness of the belly.
Sense the star in the starlight emanating from your center.
Lighting up through your body.
Shining vertically to the center of your head.
Look at the shining star.
Keep looking.
The starlight.
End of round three.
Round four.
Let us look at the star deep in the center of gravity.
Surrounded by darkness of the belly.
The increasing and expanding darkness.
Starts to cover the starlight.
As the star fades away into the darkness.
Look at the darkness surrounding the center of gravity.
Gaze at the darkness of the belly.
Look at the space of dark.
Deep in the belly.
The vast darkness below.
Look at the vast darkness.
Continue to look at the dark in the belly.
End of round four.
Round five.
Now visualize the cosmic sky in front of you.
Gaze at stars then at the darkness.
Move closer to the stars.
Disappear away.
Move beyond stars towards darkness.
See the deep dark beyond all planets, galaxies, darkness in front of you.
Darkness approaching to your face.
Touch the darkness.
Stay in the dark.
End of round five.
Round six.
Visualize a single star in the dark sky.
Start starlight coming in your direction.
See how the star is moving closer to you.
The sun is forming into an image of sun in front of you.
The sun is moving closer.
The giant sun in front of you.
The space of sun.
The sunlight.
You merge into the sun.
End of round six.