Welcome to QM3 training by all here.
It is designed to train in six rounds consisting of three minutes each with one minute break
in between.
The purpose of this particular training is to train the ability to quickly mobilize
meditative attention towards the same meditative state.
This practice is centered on witnessing the presence of air, a fine and invisible object.
We will now begin in ten seconds.
Observe the presence of air in front of you.
Observe the presence of air.
Readiness the presence of air, do not follow, it is a movement, don't follow your breathing.
Observe the presence of air in front of your face.
Do not follow the air, do not follow your breathing.
Readiness the presence of air, the air is moving on its own.
The body is breathing by itself, you are just the witness, how it is all happening by itself.
Just witness the presence of air in front of you.
And of round one.
Round two.
Witness the presence of air in front of your face.
Observe the presence of air, let the body breathe by itself.
The air moving on its own, do not participate, just watch the presence of air,
do not follow the air, stay a witness of air in front of you.
Don't follow your breathing, don't follow the air.
The air in front of you.
Witness the air in front of you.
The presence of air.
The air.
And of round two.
Round three.
The presence of air in front of you.
Be a witness without following, without participating.
Stay a witness of air in front of you.
Let the body breathe by itself.
The air move on its own.
Stay a witness.
Do not follow the air movement.
Remain for witness.
The presence of air in front of you.
All around you.
Remain for witness.
And round three.
Round four.
Observe the presence of air.
There is only air.
Remain for witness.
Don't follow just witness the presence.
The air in front of you.
Don't follow the air movement.
Do not participate.
Witness the air.
Remain for witness.
Round five.
The presence of air.
Remain for witness.
Without taking part.
The presence of air.
Remain for witness.
Let the body breathe by itself.
Don't follow the body.
Remain for witness.
And round five.
Round six.
Remain for witness.
Don't follow the breathing.
And round six.
Remain for witness.