Let's turn the mind towards the breathing process.
Notice how the body is exhaling, inhaling,
attention on the breathing body.
Watch how the body is breathing.
The natural breathing process from thinking to breathing.
Allow your body to breathe freely, naturally.
The breathing body.
When thoughts arise, shift from thought to breath.
Observe your breathing process from thought to breath.
Back to breath.
End of round one.
Prepare for the next round, in which we will shift our attention towards the breathing body.
Mind on the breathing body.
Observe how your body is breathing.
How the air is coming out of your body, going in.
Observe your breathing process.
Watch the natural breathing of your body.
Back to breath from thinking to breathing.
The breathing body.
Back to the breath.
Observe the natural breathing process.
End of round two.
Prepare for the next round.
We'll begin in three, two, one.
Attention on the breathing process of your body.
Watch the exhale and the inhale.
Watch how the body is breathing.
Allow your body to breathe naturally.
Observe how it's breathing without your help.
Just to witness the natural breathing.
Just wait and watch your breath.
Back to breath.
From thought to breath.
End of round three.
Let's prepare and plan for the next round.
In three, two, one.
Mind on the breathing body.
The breathing body.
The inhale.
Observe the gentle movement of the air.
In and out of your body.
Observe your breathing process.
From thought to breathing.
The breathing body.
Back to the breath.
During this break, you can open your eyes.
Move your arms or your body as you refresh and prepare for the next round.
Let us prepare for the next round.
Watch how the body is breathing.
Continue to watch your breathing.
Observe your breath.
There is an only breathing.
Observe your breathing.
Your breathing or non-breathing.
There is the breathing.
And the round 5.
You may want to open your eyes, move your body if need be.
This is our one minute break, when we refresh our attention.
Prepare for the next round, let us close the eyes.
When we begin in 2, 1, back to observing your breathing body, how the body is
breathing.
Watch the slow movement of your breathing, of the air.
Just wait and witness your breathing.
Or non-breathing.
Continue observing your breath.
Witness this moment.
End of round 6.
In the next round, there will be no guidance, and you will be practicing on your run,
with your attention on the breathing process and the breathing body.
Prepare for the last 6th round of self guidance, in 3, 2, 1.
End of round 6.
You have now practiced breath and self observation in multiple rounds.
And you can take such practice with you to any place, any time, where you can pause and practice for any period of time, even 40 seconds or 1 minute or 3 minutes or 5 minutes.
Whether you are waiting for a train or inside a bus, if you are sitting in an office,
at any location, you can simply turn inward and practice the breathing body and the breathing process observation.
If you are sitting in an office, you can time yourself to 3 minutes and practice in multiple rounds or even simply practice for 3 minutes.
And if you keep practicing throughout the day, you can build the meditation times throughout the day and meditate frequently, anytime, anywhere.
Even if you are at a restaurant or any sort of location, you can step out for a moment and simply turn inward towards yourself to quickly reconnect your mind and body together.
Meditate everywhere.
Thank you.