Let us trigger the practice by making a long exhalation, exhale from the nose, from the chest,
from the belly, and empty yourself of air. Allow the body to inhale freely, onto the body of empty of air.
Exhale again from the nose, from the chest, from the belly.
Focus on exhalation in a vertical top-down from the top, from the chest. Pull the belly in to push out the air.
Inhale as your body desires, shallow or deep.
Keep your attention on exhalation, from the nose, from the chest, from the belly.
With the next exhalation, bring your attention to your chest area,
reach exhale, bring your mind lower towards the abdominal area,
from the top, from the chest, and as your exhale from the belly, bring your mind towards the center of gravity.
Use the exhalation to help your mind lower towards the belly.
On the next exhale down, connect with your center of gravity.
Pull the belly in, push out the air, and stay in the center of gravity.
Prepare for the next round.
We shall begin in three, two, one.
Exhale from the nose, from the chest, from the belly, and empty yourself of air before you inhale.
Inhale easily onto your empty body.
Exhale from the top, from the chest, pull the belly in to push out the air.
Allow your body to inhale easily into internal emptiness.
Again, vertical exhalation from the top, from the chest, from the belly.
On the next exhale down, bring your mind lower into your torso.
With the exhale, bring your attention towards your abdominal area.
With each exhale, bring your mind and connect with the lower abdomen towards the area of the belly.
Exhale and reach lower towards the darkness of the belly.
Reach and connect with the center of gravity.
Pull the belly in a little more, push out the air and connect with the center.
From thought to the center of gravity.
Let go of any breathing, just stay in the center.
Thought comes in, exhale from the belly and connect with the center of gravity.
Exhale and reach lower towards the darkness of the belly.
Prepare for the next round.
We shall begin in 3, 2, 1.
Exhale from the top, from the chest, from the belly and empty yourself of air.
Attention and exhalation from the nose, from the chest, from the belly.
Allow your body to inhale easily, into the internal emptiness.
From the chest, pull the belly inward to push out the air and empty yourself of air.
With the next exhale, lower your attention towards the abdominal area.
With each exhale, bring your attention lower towards the belly.
Pull the belly inward to push out the air and reach the center of your belly.
Exhale and connect with the center of gravity.
Allow your body to inhale as desired.
Continue reaching and connecting with the center of gravity with each exhale.
From the nose, from the chest, pull the belly inward and stay in the center of gravity.
When the floor comes in, exhale from the belly and stay in the center of gravity.
Back to center.
Exhale and connect with the center of gravity.
Prepare for the next round and we begin in 3, 2, 1.
Inhale freely, easily, onto your empty body.
From the top, from the chest, pull the belly inward to push out the air from your body.
Now, use your exhale to bring your mind lower to the abdominal area.
Lower abdomen towards the belly.
With each exhale, bring your attention lower towards the center of gravity.
From thinking to centering in the point of gravity.
Use your exhale to bring yourself lower to the belly.
From thought to the center.
Back to center.
Deep in the belly.
When thoughts arise, exhale.
From the chest, from the belly, connect with the center of gravity.
Exhale and center.
From thinking to centering in the center.
Now, prepare for round 5 in which you will be guiding yourself to connect with your center of gravity.
Use your vertical exhalation to help you reach your center of gravity effectively.
At some point of the practice, you may release the exhaling and any breathing and just fully connect and maintain the link with the center of gravity.
As thoughts arise, drive them back to the center of gravity.
At some point of the practice, you may use your vertical exhalation to help you reach your center of gravity.
End of round 5.
Well done.
You have practiced in multiple rounds how to connect with your center of gravity.
You have practiced exhalation in a vertical way to first amplify yourself of air
and then utilize it to connect with your area of the belly.
To establish the connection between the mind and the point of gravity.
This way, we gradually develop the internal presence.
The vertical link from the point of gravity all the way up to the mind.
This way, we develop the inner presence and thereby developing the sense of being at home within yourself.
We also enhance the internal connection within your own body and your vital centers between the mind and the center of gravity.
Practice this in multiple rounds and in long sessions, depending on your schedule, anytime, anywhere.