Welcome to the Silent Mind program, all hears journey into a quiet and attentive way of
being. The following series is a vertical progression toward advanced meditation practice.
It is composed of three parts. The first part is accessible to everyone, including complete
novices looking for their first meditative experience or seasoned practitioners seeking
to develop a greater mind-body connection. Parts two and three develop further meditation
in depth, sustain stability and bring practitioners closer to the silence of mind.
Each part should be practiced progressively and each stage should be repeated until you
are able to practice on your own without guidance. If you are close to our Geneva Centre,
we recommend combining this course with our six-week program, which includes on-site
practice combined with training on our Silent Mind XR platform. If you only have access
to this app, you may choose to stay connected with us by subscribing to our newsletter updates
and social networks. This introductory section will provide you with practical advice on how
to begin your meditation journey. Continuity is what matters and each step is meaningful.
Now simply dive in and let your Silent Mind journey unfold.