At the heart of our practice is the development of the silent mind.
It is a practical method to reduce fluctuations of consciousness and cultivate a profound
sense of stability and self consolidation. It starts from a basic observation. Most
of us spend the day constantly engaging with many objects and many thoughts. It causes
our mental, emotional and physical potential to be divided into a thousand things.
In silent mind, we bring consciousness back to ourselves and develop a sense of wholeness
and self consolidation. We reduce random mind wandering through self awareness and
sustained attention. Even short moments of this state can enhance
our clarity and sense of inner fulfillment. With continued practice, we can live better
by transforming from within and empowering for a lifetime yourself and the others.